Guide to the Philip Agee Papers TAM.517
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV, Government Documents
  - US Department of Justice. Office of Privacy and Information Appeals (OPIA): Released Documents (25-41), 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - US Department of State: "Certificate of Acknowledgment of Execution of an Instrument", Jun 10, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - US Department of State: Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - US Department of State: Correspondence with All American Diplomatic Posts Re: Publication of "Inside the Company", 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - US Department of State: Correspondence with US Air Force, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - US Department of State: Angola, Feb 16, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - US Department of State: Australia, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - US Department of State: Barbados, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - US Department of State: Belgium, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - US Department of State: Bolivia, Aug 1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - US Department of State: Canada, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - US Department of State: Chile, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - US Department of State: Colombia, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - US Department of State: Denmark, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - US Department of State: Ecuador, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - US Department of State: Ethiopia, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - US Department of State: Fiji, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - US Department of State: Finland, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - US Department of State: France, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - US Department of State: Germany, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - US Department of State: Great Britain, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - US Department of State: Great Britain, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - US Department of State: Great Britain: List of Withheld documents, Press Coverage, Correspondence, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - US Department of State: Great Britain: Scotland, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - US Department of State: Greece, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - US Department of State: Guyana, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - US Department of State: India, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - US Department of State: Iran, 1970s-1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - US Department of State: Israel, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - US Department of State: Italy, 1976, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - US Department of State: Jamaica: List of Withheld documents, Press Coverage, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - US Department of State: Jamaice - Released Documents, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - US Department of State: Mexico, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - US Department of State: Netherlands, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - US Department of State: New Zealand, Apr 1975 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - US Department of State: Norway, Jan 30, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - US Department of State: Peru, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - US Department of State: Portugal, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - US Department of State: Singapore, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - US Department of State: South Africa, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - US Department of State: Spain, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - US Department of State: Sri Lanka, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - US Department of State: Sweden, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - US Department of State: Trinidad and Tobago, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - US Department of State: Turkey, Nov 1975 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - US Department of State: Uruguay, Undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - US Department of State: USSR, Nov 1978 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - US Department of State: Zambia, Sep 1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - US Department of the Treasury: Internal Revenue Service: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - US FBI: FOIPA deleted page information sheets, released documents: 105-223351-5, 105-223351-37, 1972, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - US FBI: FOIPA deleted page information sheets, released documents: 105-223351-38, 105-223351-63, 1972-1973, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - US FBI: FOIPA deleted page information sheets, released documents 105-223351-64, 105-223351-94, 1973-1975, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - US FBI: FOIPA deleted page information sheets, released documents 105-223351-95, 105-223351-139, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - US FBI: FOIPA deleted page information sheets, released documents 105-223351-140, 105-223351-236, 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - US FBI Headquarters: List of Released Documents, Undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - US FBI Headquarters: List of Released Documents (includes descriptions of withheld portions), Undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - US FBI: Released Documents, 1971-1972, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - US Information Agency, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - US International Communication Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Series V, Legal Cases and Documents
  Series V, Legal Cases and Documents, documents five lawsuits in which Agee was the plaintiff, and also contains a selection of legal documents from and correspondence with Agee's attornerys regarding other cases that were of interest to Agee. The majority of the series consists of affadavits and other legal documents from Agee's suit v. the United States Central Intelligence Agency, Federal Bureau of Investigation, National Security Agency, Department of State, and Department of Justice, seeking to obtain government documents under the Freedom of Information Act. There are a small number of files, chiefly legal correspondence, but with some legal documents, from two lawsuits in which Agee sought damages for allegedly being falsely accused of being responsible for the 1975 death of Athens, Greece CIA Station Chief Richard Welch. In this regard, Agee separately sued former First Lady Barbara Bush, charging that her Barbara Bush: A Memoir (1994) falsely made this claim. Agee also sued author George Crile, et al, on the same grounds re his book Charlie Wilson's War (Grove/Atlantic, 2003). Bush agreed to alter one paragraph in her book as per a 1997 settlement. For the Crile case a similar settlement was reached in 2004. From Agee's unsuccessful attempt to regain his passport by suing the Department of State are several files of clippings, correspondence, and legal documents. There is also one file of plaintiff's affadavits from the case Philip Agee v. United States of America: Civil Action No. 94-2020-WBB, To Recover Damages for Illegal and Tortious Acts Committed against the Plaintiff by the CIA.
  - Subseries V-A, Agee v. Barbara Bush
    This subseries documents the case between Barbara Bush and Agee who accused her of falsely accusing Agee, in Barbara Bush: A Memoir (Scribner, 1994), of being responsible for the death of Richard Welch CIA Athens Station Chief, killed in 1975 by the Greek Terrorist group November 17)
    - Philip Agee v. Barbara Bush, Jan 1995-Aug 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Philip Agee v. Barbara Bush: Bills, Correspondence (Legal), Jan 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Philip Agee v. Barbara Bush: Clippings, 1977-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Philip Agee v. Barbara Bush et al.: Invoices from Law Offices Bernabei and Katz, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Philip Agee v. Barbara Bush: Philip Agee Defense Fund (Checks, Correspondence), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V-B, Agee v. George Crile, Gust Avrakotos, Grove/Atlantic., the Atlantic Monthly Press, and Publishers Group West
    The case claimed that Crile's book Charlie Wilson's War [Grove/Atlantic, 2003] contained false allegations that Agee was responsible for the death of Athens CIA Station Chief Richard Welsh.
    - Philip Agee v. George Crile, et. al.: Correspondence, Jun 2004-Mar 2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Philip Agee v. George Crile, etl al.: Legal Documents, Jun 2004-Oct 2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Philip Agee v. George Crile, et al.: Settlement, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Philip Agee v. United States of America: Civil Action No. 94-2020-WBB
    The case was filed to recover damages for illegal and tortious acts committed against the plaintiff by the CIA.
    - Plaintiff's Affadavits and Correspondence with His Attorney Melvin Wulf., 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Subseries V-D, Agee v. United States Central Intelligence Agency, Federal Bureau of Investigation, National Security Agency, Department of State, and Department of Justice
    The case sought to obtain government documents under the Freedom of Information Act.
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit Charles E. Wilson, Executive Secretary to the Publications Review Board, Jan 30, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Clayton E. McManaway, Deputy Assistant Secretary of State and Director of the Center for Classification and Declassification, Feb 29, 1980, Jun 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of David Stevens Byerly, Special Agent of the FBI, Jul 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavits of Frank M. Machak, Chief of Document and Reference Division of the Foreign Affairs Document and Reference Center of the Department of State, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Graham W. Van Note, Special Agent of the FBI, Feb 29, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Hugh James McMenamin, Special Agent of the FBI, Feb 29, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavits of John E. Bacon, Information and Privacy Coordinator of the CIA, Jun 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavits of John N. McMahon, Deputy Director for Operations of the CIA, Jan 30, 1980, Apr 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Launie M. Ziebell, Assistant General Counsel for the CIA, Jan 28, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavits of Louis J. Dube, Information Review Officer of the Directorate of Operations of the CIA, Sep 15, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Maurice A. Sovern, Chief of the Information, Privacy and Litigation Group, Directorate of Operations, CIA, Sep 17, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Melvin L. Wulf, Plaintiff's Attorney, Jul 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Michael M. Roman, Special Agent of the FBI, Aug 21, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Myron I. Weinstein, Deputy Director of the United states Secret Service, May 28, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Philip Agee, Jun 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Richard Stover, Special Agent of the FBI - Itemization, Indexing and Description of Classified Information Withheld from Plaintiff Persuant to 5 USC, Jun 25, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Robert W. Gambind, Director of Security, CIA, Jan 30, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Roy R. Banner, Chief of Policy Staff of the National Security Agency, Jul 1, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Stansfield Turner, Director of CIA, Jan 29, 1980, Sep 19, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of Thomas W. Ainsworth, Acting Deputy Assistant Secretary of State for Classification and Declassification, Sep 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Affidavit of William R. Kotapish, Director of the Office of Security of the CIA, Mar 24, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Court Orders, Notes, Notices, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Declaration of F. Henry Habicht II, Special Assistant to the Attorney General of the United States, Sep 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Declaration of James P. Turner, Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General of the Civil Rights Division of the Department of Justice, Dec 17, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Declaration of Jean Kornblut, Paralegal Specialist of the Department of Justice, Sep 10, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Declaration of Richard L. Huff, Acting Director of the Office of Privacy and Information Appeals, Dec 11, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Declaration of E. Ross Buckley, Attorney in the Office of Legal Support Services Criminal Division, Department of Justice, Sept 15, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: CIA's Statement of Material Facts, As To Which There Is No General Issue, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Department of Justice's Motion for Partial Reconsideration of Motion for Partial Summary Judgment (Includes Related Memorandum, Order), Aug 1980-Sep 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Department of Justice's Motion for Partial Summary Judgment (Includes Plaintiff's Memorandum), Apr 1980 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: National Security Agency's Motion for Summary Judgment, Related Statement, Order, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Defendants' Points and Authorities in Opposition to Plaintiff's Motion for a More Particularized Justification of Nondisclosure and in SUpport of Defendant CIA's Motion for Partial Judgment (Includes Court Order), undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Document: Disposition Index Volume 1 0001-0999, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Document: Disposition Index Volume 2-3 0200-0399, Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Document: Disposition Index Volume 4-5 0400-0599, Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Document: Disposition Index Volume 6-7 0600-0799, Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Document: Disposition Index Volume 8-9 0800-0999, Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Judge Gerhard A. Gesell's Memorandum re: the CIA, Jul 17, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Intervenor-Defendant United States' Motion for a Preliminary Injunction, Related Court Order, Jan 29, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Hearing on Cross-motions for Summary Judgment, Proceedings, Sep 12, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Plaintiff's Complaint, Oct 8, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Plaintiff's Motion for Particularized Justification of Nondisclosure of CIA Documents (Includes related memorandum, statement), Jun 4, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Reports to the Court, Plaintiff's Response to the Reports, Apr 1981-Dec-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Response of the Intervenor-Defendant United States to Plaintiff's Motion for Reconsideration of the Court's Order Granting Intervention, Mar 24, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Plaintiff's Memorandum and Motion to Vacate the Court's Order of February 21, 1980 and to Voluntarily Dismiss His FOIA Suit, Feb 1980-Mar 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Plaintiff's Statement of Genuine Issues, Jun 13, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Research Files, Copies of Court Decisions, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Stipulation to an Enlargement of Time, Feb 12, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: United States' Motion and Memorandum to Intervene as a Defendant for Joinder of the United States as a Party to the Action; Plaintiff's Opposition, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: USA, Intervening Defendant/Counterclaiman; Court Orders, Jul 1980-May 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Defendant United States' Opposition to Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgment and Reply to Plaintiff's Opposition to US Motion for Summary Judgment, Sep 3, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Plaintiff's Filing of Hearings on CIA Publication Review Process Before the House Select Committee on Intelligence (Transcript) Mar 6, 1980, Jul 14, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: USA, Intervening Defendant/Counterclaimant: Memorandums, Jul 1980-Oct 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Motion of Defendant United States and cIA for a Protective Order, Sep 3, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al., USA ID: United District Judge Gerhard A. Gesell's Memorandums and Orders, Apr 1980-Oct 1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.: Request for Production of Documents, Jul 14, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.; USA (Intervening Defendant): Plaintiff's Cross-Motion for Summary Judgment With Respect to the Counterlcaim of the United States; Related Memorandum, Court Order, Statement, Jul 14, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.; USA (Intervening Defendant): Permanent Injunction; Motion for Amendment, Oct 1980-Nov 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Philip Agee v. CIA, et al.; USA (Intervening Defendant): Plaintiff's Answer to Amended Counterclaim, Apr 22, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Subseries V-E, Agee v. United States Department of State
    Revocation of Passport: Upheld by the U.S. Supreme Court, 1981)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: Clippings (English, German), 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23A)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State (Revocation of Passport): Clippings (Photocopies), 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23B)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: United States District Court for the District of Columbia, Civil Action No. 79-3491, Dec 1979-Jan 1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: No. 80-1125, Feb 1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Philip Agee v. Cyrus Vance, Secretary of State: Affidavit of Philip Agee with Attachments, Jun 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Edmund S. Muskie, Secretary of State, v. Philip Agee, Supreme Court of the United States No. 80-83, Oct 6, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Alexander Haig, Secretary of State, v. Philip Agee, Supreme Court of the United States No. 80-83, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kaplan, Stephen B.: "The CIA Responds to Its Blacksheep: Censorship and Passport Revocation - The Cases of Philip Agee" (Connecticut Law Review, Vol. 13, No. 2), Winter 1981 (Box 8, Folder 29A)
  - Subseries V-F, Other Cases of Interest to Agee
    - Attorney General of the United States v. The Irish People, Inc.: CA. No. 76-1518, Aug 8, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Charles V. Stephenson v. Internal Revenue Service, Atlanta, GA, and John W. Henderson, District Director, IRS GA No. C78-1071A, Jun 26, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Common Cause, et al. v. National Archives and Records Service: Appeal from the United states District Court for the District of Columbia CA No. 77-0297, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Congressman John M. Murphy v. Federal Bureau of Investigation, et al. CA No. 80-518, May 28, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Judith Miller, Reporter for The New York Times v. Central Intelligence Agency et al. CA 77-1029, May 6, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Ralph w. McGehee and The Nation v. William Casey, Director of Central Intelligence Agency No. 81-0734, Mar 27, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Bill B. Moorefield v. United States Secret Service, et al. No. 78-4443, Feb 18, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Nassar Afshar v. Department of State, et al. CA No. 76-1421, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Thomas E. Hayden v. National Security Agency/Central Security Service, et al. No. 78-1728; Jane Fonda v. National Security Agency/Central Security Service et al. No. 78-1729, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Victor L. Marchetti v. United States of America, Supreme Court of the United States No. 72-1586, Oct 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Series VI, Subject Files
  Series VI, Subject Files (1950-2006) contains research files on countries, compiled by Agee, with a concentration on Latin America, and in paraticular Cuba and Nicaragua; files on individuals, organizations and topics, in particular sets of files on Aldrich Hazen Ames (1941-, a former CIA counter-intelligence officer and analyst, who, in 1994, was convicted of spying for the Soviet Union and Russia, which included revealing the names of CIA agents), and on Project Democracy, a Reagan-era foreign policy initiative; and files, including some legal documents on Agee's unsuccessful struggles against his expulsion, respectively, from Great Britain and the Netherlands. This series contains a broad range of printed ephemera, clippings files, speeches, internal documents of various organizations, and some letters.
  - Subseries VI-A, Countries: Latin America and the Caribbean
    - Argentina, 1983-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Argentina: Commission of Human Rights (C.A.D.H.U: Comision Argentina De Derechos Humanos), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia, Sep 2, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Brazil, 1968-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chile (Manuscripts Included By Raymond Paredes-Ahlgren and John Dinges), 1975-1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Cuba (English), 1977-2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Cuba (Spanish), 1979-2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Cuba: Radio Havana, Dec 1993-Jan 1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Cuba: Radio Havana, Dec 1993-Jan 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Cuba: The Free Trade with Cuba Act, HR 2229 - Joint Hearing of the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures and the Subcommittee on Trade of the Ways and Means Committee, Statements by Congressman Jose E. Serrano; Randolph C. Lumb, Vice President, Government Affairs, AT&T, Julie M. Feinsilver, Ph.D, Mar 17, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - El Salvador, 1981-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ecuador, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Grenada, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Grenada: La Barraca Theater Company, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Grenada: The Solidarity Group of Grenada, Apr 6, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Guatemala, 1981-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Haiti, Feb 1985-Mar 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Honduras, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Jamaica, 1977-1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Jamaica Workers Solidarity Campaign (Against US and CIA), Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Latin America (General), 1976-1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Latin America: Fenton Communications Media Report, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Latin American Studies Syllabi, Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Latin American Anti-Communist Politicians, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mexico, 1975-1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Nicaragua, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Nicaragua, 1981-Jun 1984 (Box 9, Folder 26A)
    - Nicaragua, Jul 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Nicaragua, 1985-1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Nicaragua: Contras: US Backed Anti Government Guerrilla Group (Clippings), 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Nicaragua and Honduras: Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Nicaragua (The CIA Manual Distributed for Anti-Government Forces in Nicaragua): Distributed by the Center for Constitutional Rights Before the House Committee on Intelligence, Dec 4, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Nicaragua: Miskito Indians, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - North American Congress on Latin America, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Office of the Americas, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Panama, 1989-1990, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Paraguay: Archivo Del Terror, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Peace March in Central America, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Peru, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Quotations by Agee and Other Notable Individuals on Latin America, 1960s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 39)